A sound soul, dwells within a sound mind, and a sound body.
Welcome to Death Weapon Meister Academy.
More commonly known as the DWMA.
It stands as a defense against the forces of evil, which would plunge the world into chaos and drag humanity to the very depths of fear and madness.
The demons known as Keishin, and their insatiable hunger for destruction.
To ensure the Keishin never regain their hold on this world, this academy was founded by the Grim Reaper, Death himself.
So basically, we're an organization that exists to protect and preserve peace.
I guess it's not exactly a typical school.
Oh well, that isn't important. For now, let's roll up our sleeves and get to work!
einem
魂の火が胸を刺すなら 言葉よりもっと強い響きが今聞こえるか
六人目も合わさず 運命まで絡んでく 行き先もらったポテル 食えない夜の端で
不可愛しすぎた眩しさが 悪い夢に続いても
繋いだ魂の火が胸を刺すなら 言葉よりもっと強い響きが今聞こえるか
やっと理由は途絶びに惹きつけられて 触れた瞬間の傷の分だけ確かになれる
ご視聴ありがとうございました
Patty, your stances off again, the two of you aren't in a line.
Oh!
I'm sorry, kid.
Uh, kid, do you really think now is the time to be worrying about that?
Yes, I do.
I want it to be perfect every time.
I know, but do you think that this works, maybe?
How many times do I have to tell you everything must be in perfect balance?
Symmetry is what makes the world beautiful.
He ran away, he ran away!
Patty, why can't you be quiet and listen to what I'm talking?
Is that so much to ask, huh?
Okay.
Symmetry is key.
Everything must be aesthetically pleasing.
Oh, wonderful. Here we go.
That's why I use the two of you as twin pistols in order to preserve symmetry.
When I hold you both, I'm completely balanced on the right and left.
It isn't perfect because your human forms are so different from each other, though.
Your hairstyles and height, for example.
Even your boobs are different sizes!
Excuse me for being smaller than my little sister!
What night do you have to talk about symmetry anyway?
Three stripes on the left side of your hair and none on the right?
That doesn't look symmetrical to me!
You're right! I'm an abomination!
I'm filthy and dirty and unbalanced!
Why is there only one set of stripes?
I'm garbage!
A symmetrical garbage!
I deserve to die!
Yeah, and here we go.
Patty?
Yes!
Now, now, kid, you can't forget that you're a grim reaper.
Compared to that, what do three little lines matter?
Yeah, kid, you're not garbage!
If you were garbage, then you'd smell a lot worse!
So why don't we just get up and try again, okay?
You don't think I'm asymmetrical garbage, really?
No, of course not!
Garbage is ew, and you're not!
All right, then.
Let's report to my father.
Not the sharpest tool in the shed, is he?
These little rich kids are always so gullible.
Well, hello, son! What's up?
It's good to see you!
I've forgotten how cute those stripes in your hair are!
Stop it, Dad.
I'm not a little kid anymore.
Is that really necessary?
That's a sensitive topic right now, sir!
Huh?
Okay, then. We'll just move along.
How are things going?
It looks like you're making some good progress collecting Kishan souls.
But, kid, don't forget, you're a grim reaper.
You don't really need to be training weapons or reclaiming souls.
Even so, I want to make my own weapons to my own specifications.
Huh.
In that case, since you have two weapons,
the number of souls you must collect is double the normal amount.
This means you'll have to work harder, too, Liz and Patty.
Yes, sir!
I understand.
And I would like to collect all of the souls that I need in one go.
So, do you have any suitable targets for me right now?
Ah, well, now that you mention it,
as a matter of fact, I do have one.
What's going on there?
Hey!
Soul!
Maka!
Oh, hey, guys. Good morning.
Morning, Maka.
Soul.
What happened?
Why is everyone down here?
Seriously?
You mean you haven't heard yet?
It's kind of a hot topic around here right now.
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
Oh, I get it.
Everyone's scared of what a big star I'm becoming, huh?
Not quite, Black Star.
It has nothing to do with you.
Huh?
The Perfect Boy.
Death the Kid's magnificent mission.
In the heart of the scorching Egyptian desert,
there is an ancient ruin.
It is known as the Pyramid of Anubis.
You will find a witch there, a necromancer.
She's raised a great number of the dead
who were entombed in the pyramid.
Every night, she leads out these mummies
to feed on human souls.
A necromancer is difficult to stop.
Her first set of mummies will be sent out
to create another set,
which will in turn create yet another
until she eventually has an entire army of mummies.
The ancient Pyramid of Anubis, I see.
It was built at a time when all construction
followed strict theories of symmetry.
Sounds great.
Actually, I was originally thinking about
assigning a three-star meister to this one.
Don't worry, Dad.
I can handle it myself.
After I've defeated the witch,
I can take some time to enjoy the architecture.
So, what do you guys think?
Anyone else want to go find out
who took on the big mission?
Yeah, of course I do.
Whoever this guy is, he's a real show-off.
He actually thinks he can build
a bigger reputation than mine.
Okay, then let's get going.
Hey, wait! Come back, you two!
Rocky!
Oh, would you just look at the exquisite symmetry?
All that time in weapon form
makes my back ache like crazy.
That thing's huge!
I could do without all this dust.
Let's all go inside, then, okay?
Are we sure that we want to do this?
This place gives me the crease.
It's okay. I'm sure we'll be fine.
Let's go!
My eyes itch.
Wow.
It's perfect on the inside, too.
I hate it here.
I don't do well in creepy, dusty, icky places.
Hey, sis, I've been wondering something.
How come everyone always closes their eyes
when they sneeze?
Is it to keep their eyes
from popping out of their heads?
Do you know?
I don't know, Patty.
That is certainly one theory
that might explain why it is.
Of course, it could also be
an involuntary reflex
triggered by normal brain activity.
Hmm.
Maybe I could do a test next time
I have a cold and tape my eyelids open.
Yes, but what if your theory is right
and your eyeballs do pop out of your head?
Okay, yeah.
You might be right there, big sis.
You're so smart.
Kid, what's wrong with you?
You've been quiet for a long time now.
Well, uh, maybe it's my imagination,
but I have this horrible feeling
that the painting that I have
hanging in my living room
is leaning a little bit to the right.
Does that stop the painting
really matter right now?
Yes, of course it matters.
What should I do?
I can't go on like this.
I can't wait.
I have to go back and make sure.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
There's a limit to the insanity
I'll put up with.
You can worry about it when we get home.
I'm worrying about it.
Don't worry.
I won't let you worry about it.
I'm worrying.
Shut up!
You spoiled brat.
I'm worrying.
Oh, no, it's a mummy.
Mummy, mummy, mummy.
Mummy!
Hey, they're kind of cute, aren't they?
Mummy, lick me!
Mummy, splatter!
How could this happen to me?
It's time to transform, Patty.
Okay.
Hey, kid, let's go.
Huh?
I don't know.
Dear Liz and Patty,
I'm still worrying about it.
Nothing you can say will help.
I'm going back home at once
to check on the painting.
Watch your step.
It's dark in the pyramid.
Death, the kid.
He's joking, right?
Patty!
Right!
Beat it, mummy!
Patty, don't stick me in that monster's dirty mouth!
Ew!
Okay, sorry!
Ancient statue, I lend you the dark heart from my body,
that you may live again and do my bidding!
Awaken, pharaoh!
Your master is calling you!
The laugh of the pharaoh!
He's got me!
I'm being dragged in!
He's going to eat my soul!
There is no one in this world
who can ever be my master.
All who enter,
beware the wrath of the pharaoh.
Where do you suppose those two idiots
have run off to now?
Ah, just my imagination, after all.
It's perfect.
And now, the girls are waiting for me to come back.
I should get going.
That's it.
We've recovered every last one of the mummy's souls.
Do we have them all evenly split up?
Mm-hmm.
Since Kid would get all depressed if we didn't divide them up evenly.
I don't like this.
Did you hear that creepy noise coming from over that way?
Let's just go.
Why don't we wait until Kid comes back?
Nah, it'll be okay.
I've got my big sis here with me.
Oh, no.
The noise.
It's coming from down here.
Quietly, Patty.
We need to be quiet.
I got it.
Oh, no.
Did you see that thing move over there?
Don't do that, Patty.
It isn't funny.
Oh, dear.
Time left over.
Huh?
What are you two doing here?
The bell rang.
Your classes have already started.
What are we doing?
What about you?
You're a teacher, right?
Shouldn't you be in class, too?
I have other things to take care of right now.
I'm a teacher and a busy man.
You two should move along.
Yeah, we will.
But before we get going, there's something we need you to tell us about first.
We want to know about the Pyramid of Anubis.
Who signed up to take the mission?
Ah, that mission wasn't taken by a student from our school.
It's much too difficult for one of you.
If not one of us, then who took it?
It was taken by Lord Death's son.
Lord Death has a son?
Well, I'll be damned.
Really?
Yes, really.
I'm not a man to tell a lie.
He's a grim reaper, just like his father.
His name is Death the Kid.
Nice to see you again, Anubis.
You're even more beautiful than the last time we met.
What are you?
Such perfect symmetry.
You are amazing.
Kate, no.
You make me sick!
Get away!
How incredibly disappointing.
Liz?
Patty?
Kid here.
Didn't mean to intrude.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
What is this?
You two hurry up and switch to weapon form.
Our powers don't work with us wrapped up in these bandages.
What?
Tornado!
Blitz!
Okay.
And go!
A pharaoh's soul, huh?
Now it will be mine.
What's happening, kid?
Are you okay?
Kid, why don't you do something?
This isn't like you.
Look at the pharaoh closely.
He is...
...perfectly symmetrical in every way.
Ah!
Kid!
Forget about the symmetry.
It doesn't matter right now.
You'll die if you don't do something fast.
You're supposed to become a great grim reaper with us as your weapons.
Don't let us down.
No, I can't.
I can't pull the trigger on him.
Kid!
The wrath of the pharaoh.
Wrath.
Wrath!
I will come and deliver the final blow myself.
Wrath.
Right.
Left.
Wrath.
you're disgustingly hideous it's all over now what the hell kind of thing are you i've never seen
anything so messed up in my life do you know nothing about symmetry whoever made you should
be dug up from his grave shot and be buried you make me violently ill just look at your forehead
you don't deserve such a jewel in fact you don't even deserve to exist
disgusting disgusting disgusting disgusting disgusting disgusting disgusting you are disgusting
disgusting disgusting
i feel much better now
kid we collected an odd number of souls this time so i have one more than patty
damn it i can't handle that we need another mission okay i want to put this whole episode behind me
that pharaoh was absolutely horrific at any rate the mission is over let's say goodbye to the
beautiful anubis
you broke the pharaoh
uh what'd we do you went a little nuts in there don't you think crazy
i'm a pig a laus a useless cow i destroyed anubis such utter garbage cannot be allowed to live i deserve
to die no you don't need to die i mean who hasn't destroyed one or two pyramids in their life really
see it's okay girls thank you
why are your breasts still two different sizes
as punishment for destroying the pyramid of anubis all of the souls you've collected will be confiscated
damn it i'm garbage i'll die
there is the sightmeister maka and her partner and weapon soul eater
the assassin black star with the magic dark arm subaki
and lord death's son death the kid with his twin pistols liz and patty the thompson sisters
the prologue is complete and now the real story can begin
well
it
fun
The universe is
black
Black
white
Bye
間に合う筈だから
I wanna be the best
絶望と一緒に
悲鳴を上げ 突き刺され
全てが変わる前に
I want to be here!
Please tell me it isn't true!
Calm down. It's only an extra class.
But why am I in it?
On the next episode of Soul Eater,
engage the witch hunter.
A remedial lesson in the graveyard?
Watch it, or I'll take your soul.